<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>TimeMachine [Fixed]</name>
    <directory>timemachinefixed</directory>
    <id>3169946719</id>
    <description>Machines and beggars speed up while you use them, saving your real-world time without breaking the in-game timer.

This is a maintained version of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2617557401]TimeMachine[/url] by @tarako. You only need to enable TimeMachine [Fixed]; the original mod is not required.

SUPPORTED

- Slot Machine and Fortune Telling Machine
- Crane Game
- Blood Donation Machine and Confessional
- Shell Game and Hell Game
- Greed Donation Machine
- Beggar, Devil Beggar, Key Master, Bomb Bum, Battery Bum, and Rotten Beggar
- Multiplayer

KEY FIXES

- Fixed Boss Rush, Hush, and Mausoleum Boss Rush entrances failing to open when reached within their time limits.
- Fixed crashes involving Soul of the Forgotten, Soul of Jacob and Esau, Strawman, or Found Soul when using Blood Donation Machines.
- Fixed players passing through beggars, being pushed to an abnormal distance, or teleporting at high speed.

SAFETY &amp; CONFIGURATION

Configure maximum speed, acceleration, and individual machine toggles with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3701683951]Mod Config Menu[/url].

- Flies spawned by shell games, hell games, and beggars are removed so accelerated interactions cannot hurt you (MCM: KillSpawnedFlies, on by default).
- Troll bombs from machines and beggars are delayed until the interaction ends (MCM: DefuseSpawnedBombs, on by default).
- Acceleration stops when the next donation could kill you, including the increased Blood Donation Machine damage from Womb onward (MCM: PreventSuddenDeath, on by default).
- The Lost using The Chariot, Keeper, and a recently revived Lazarus are handled safely. Disable PreventSuddenDeath if you intentionally want to donate rapidly while invincible.
- Player speed and the in-game timer accelerate with the machine to prevent unintended advantages.

让机器和乞丐在连续使用时越来越快，节省现实时间，同时保持游戏内计时公平。

本修复版支持老虎机、预言机、娃娃机、献血机、告解室、三选一游戏、贪婪存款机以及各种乞丐，并支持多人游戏。只需启用 TimeMachine [Fixed]，无需同时启用旧版。

主要修复：

- 修复在时限内到达，Boss Rush、凹凸及陵墓 Boss Rush 入口仍无法开启的问题。
- 修复骨哥符文、双子符文、稻草人和复得幽魂使用献血机时导致的崩溃。
- 修复高速互动时穿过乞丐、距离异常或瞬移的问题。

所有速度与机器开关均可在 [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3701683951]Mod Config Menu[/url] 中调整。默认还会清除互动生成的苍蝇、延缓即爆炸弹，并在下一次献血可能致死时自动停止加速；这些安全功能都可以单独关闭。

发现其他问题，欢迎留言反馈！

┌──────────────────────────────────────────────────────────┐
│★ Check out my other fixed mod: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2916069863]GoodTrip [Fixed][/url] ★│
└──────────────────────────────────────────────────────────┘
</description>
    <version>1.25</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
</metadata>
