<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>GoodTrip [Fixed]</name>
    <directory>goodtripfixed</directory>
    <id>2916069863</id>
    <description>[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1630477831]GoodTrip[/url] with BUGs &amp; compatibility fixed:

- Fixed Tainted Forgotten accidentally throw his bone when using TAB + ↑↓←→.
- Fixed mirror world in Downpour II when clicking mouse on the map.
- Mirror world keyboard minimap now flips as well to be intuitive.
- No longer need manually specify HUD offset in gtconfig, it automatically reads options.ini.
- Able to show mirror room and white fireplace as icon in minimap.
- Fixed compatibility with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1978904635]Minimap API[/url].
- Prevents accidental tear shoot when clicking mouse on big map.
- Keyboard minimap position is saved between runs once well placed.
- Let me know if you found other bugs or compatibility issues, I'll try to fix it!

As well as many feature improvements:

- All options below may be toggled in [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2681875787]Mod Config Menu[/url]!
- May teleport directly into an uncleared room as long as it have a cleared neighbor (MCM: AllowNeighborRoom).
- Bookmark interested rooms by pressing TAB + 1, TAB + 2, ... in that room. Press TAB + 1 again will quick teleport to that room without pain to move cursors (MCM: AllowBookmarking).
- Tab + Z to teleport back to last room visited, TAB + Z again to back to current room again (MCM: LastRoomShortcut).
- TAB + R for faster restart (MCM: FastRestartEnable).
- Controller users may set their prefered button instead for Z and R by binding ControllerAlternateZ and ControllerAlternateR in MCM (these two bindings are disabled by default until you set them).
- Show mirror room and white fireplace in Downpour II, minecart and its buttons in Mines II, tinted skull in Depths II as room icon (MCM: ShowSpecialIcons).
- May make this mod optionally ignore curse of lost (MCM: FollowCurseOfLost, not ignore by default).
- Quick teleport into neighbor room by TAB + ASWD, without pain to long holding TAB + ↑↓←→ (MCM: QuicklyOneRoomMove, not enabled by default).
- Move cursor faster by triggering TAB + ↑↓←→ once, without pain to long holding TAB + ↑↓←→ (MCM: FasterCursorMove, not enabled by default).
- Optioanlly teleport even faster by removing the annoying black screen animation (MCM: FastTransition, not enabled by default).
- Optionally compatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3071704639]Dangerous room! Caution[/url] to indicate dangerous room in color.
- Memorize keyboard minimap widget location once dragged with mouse, or tweak TopLeftX and TopLeftY manually in MCM.
- Integrated with Fair Trip: increases game time according to player move speed and teleported distance, disallowing teleporting path with non-cleared rooms in the way as well (FairTripTime, requires [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1978904635]Minimap API[/url] to work). Thanks @iamthestoat for merging this cool feature! Now hidden behind a master switch MinimapAPICompat in MCM, off by default — turn it on if you want the Fair Trip experience.
    
----------------------------
----original description----
----------------------------
HOW TO USE
A)Press Tab + mouseclick on the minimap(the room you want to go) directly.
·Make sure the current room and your target room are clean.
B)For controller or keyboard users, Press MapButton + ↑↓←→ to move the cursor for Selecting target room, in an extra minimap.
·This map can be dragged or pinned with the mouse. When it's pinned, you can click to travel without press TAB.
·If you like, you can change &quot;KeyboardMapEnable = true&quot; to &quot;false&quot; in gtconfig.lua to disable this minimap.(1.2.1 now drag it into the recycle bin just disable it fast)
·If your hudoffset in game is not 0, please change &quot;HudOffset = 0&quot; in gtconfig.lua to match your real hudoffset.
·Set &quot;TeleportAnimation = false&quot; in gtconfig.lua can remove the animation(White flash).(1.2.1:It is now disable by default)
---
tips:
·The location of gtconfig.lua:
*REPENTANCE*
// Windows
...\steam\steamapps\common\Binding of Isaac Rebirth\mods\goodtrip_1630477831\
'General modding changes:
- Mods are now stored in a &quot;mods&quot; folder in the same directory as the rest of the game files
- This directory can be easily accessed by right clicking The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth in the Steam library, then clicking on &quot;Properties&quot;, &quot;Local Files&quot;, and finally &quot;Browse...&quot;'
--
·How to show the built-in cursor:
C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Repentance\
edit options.ini
Change MouseControl=0 to MouseControl=1
------------

AB+:
// Windows
C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ Mods\goodtrip_1630477831\
// OSX
~/Library/Application Support/Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ Mods/goodtrip_1630477831/

·How to show the built-in cursor:
// Windows
C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ \
// OSX
~/Library/Application Support/Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ /
edit options.ini
Change MouseControl=0 to MouseControl=1



【操作方式】
1.按住地图键(通常是TAB)的同时，鼠标点击右上角小地图的目标房间来进行传送。
·传送需要所在房间和目标房间满足传送条件，基本上要求点亮的房间、地图以及玩家不能处在战斗中。
2.站在原地，按住地图键，用发射眼泪的方向键在「辅助地图」中移动光标选择要去的房间进行传送
·传送条件同上，这个功能是专为手柄和键盘设计的。
·「辅助地图」只有在可以传送的条件下能够呼出，亦可将之用鼠标拖动到任意位置，或点击左上角图钉将之锁定在屏幕上。
·这个地图一样可以用鼠标点击房间来进行传送，而且锁定的情况下不需要按tab直接点击即可。
·如有需要，这个地图可以在配置文件gtconfig.ini中将KeyboardMapEnable = true修改为=false来禁用。

【注意】
·游戏内如果有调整ui偏移量，须用记事本打开同目录下gtconfig.lua设置文件，找到HudOffset = 0 ←修改这个数为游戏菜单设置hud offset数值相同，范围为0~10，来进行校正；或者直接把游戏内ui偏移调整为0，否则会影响选择右上角房间的准确性。（fixed版中已经修复，现在自动同步HudOffset了）
·附加功能 TAB+R 光速重开。 可以在gtconfig文件修改FastRestartEnable开启，为了避免误按默认关闭了。（fixed版中已经默认开启，可以通过MCM配置）
【附录】
·答gtconfig.lua所在位置（fixed版中已经废弃，现在直接修改main.lua中的gtconfig即可）
！！忏悔mod在新地址！！
// Windows
...\steam\steamapps\common\Binding of Isaac Rebirth\mods\goodtrip_1630477831\
忏悔改变了mod文件夹，现在在steam里右键游戏访问游戏所在文件夹可以找到同目录下的“mods”文件夹，新的配置文件可能要在这里面更改。
胎衣+
// Windows
C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ Mods\goodtrip_1630477831\
// OSX
~/Library/Application Support/Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ Mods/goodtrip_1630477831/
·如何开启游戏内置光标（推荐）
// Windows
C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ \
(忏悔的目录是C:\Users\YourName\My Games\Binding of Isaac Repentance\)
// OSX
~/Library/Application Support/Binding of Isaac Afterbirth+ /
编辑 options.ini 文件
把 MouseControl=0 改成 MouseControl=1 并保存（fixed版中已经默认自动帮你开启）
常见问题：不小心把传送小地图拖到垃圾桶里删除了？在控制台输入一行代码 lua gt:get_config().KeyboardMapEnable=true 就能恢复
</description>
    <version>2.2.29</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Floors"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
