<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>GoodTrip [Fixed]</name>
    <directory>goodtripfixed</directory>
    <id>2916069863</id>
    <description>Teleport to cleared rooms directly from the minimap — now fixed, polished, and highly configurable.

This is a maintained version of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1630477831]GoodTrip[/url]. You only need to enable GoodTrip [Fixed]; the original mod is not required.

HOW TO USE

- Mouse: hold the map button (TAB by default), then click a room on the minimap.
- Keyboard/controller: hold the map button and use the shooting directions to select a room on the teleport map.
- Drag the teleport map anywhere you like, or pin it to click rooms without holding TAB.
- Both your current room and destination normally need to be cleared, and you cannot teleport during combat.

KEY FIXES

- Fixed Tainted Forgotten throwing his bone when navigating with TAB + ↑↓←→.
- Fixed mouse teleportation and map orientation in the Downpour II mirror world.
- HUD offset is detected automatically from options.ini.
- Fixed compatibility with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1978904635]Minimap API[/url] and Repentance+.
- Prevented accidental tear firing when clicking the teleport map.
- The teleport map remembers its position between runs.

FEATURES

Configure these features with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3701683951]Mod Config Menu[/url]:

- Bookmark rooms with TAB + 1, TAB + 2, etc.; use the same shortcut again to teleport back (MCM: AllowBookmarking).
- Return to the previously visited room with TAB + Z; press it again to return (MCM: LastRoomShortcut).
- Restart quickly with TAB + R (MCM: FastRestartEnable).
- Controller users can assign alternate buttons for the Z and R shortcuts.
- Show special-room icons: the mirror room and white fireplace in Downpour II, minecart and buttons in Mines II, and tinted skull in Depths II (MCM: ShowSpecialIcons).
- Teleport into an uncleared room when it has a cleared neighbor (MCM: AllowNeighborRoom).
- Optionally ignore Curse of the Lost (MCM: FollowCurseOfLost).
- Move quickly to a neighboring room with TAB + WASD (MCM: QuicklyOneRoomMove, off by default).
- Move the teleport-map cursor faster with TAB + ↑↓←→ (MCM: FasterCursorMove, off by default).
- Remove the black transition animation for faster teleportation (MCM: FastTransition, off by default).
- Integrate with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3071704639]Dangerous room! Caution[/url] to color dangerous rooms.
- Enable Fair Trip rules, which add time based on movement speed and teleport distance and require a cleared route (MCM: FairTripTime, off by default). Thanks @iamthestoat and @Porp!
- Bind a custom keyboard/controller button for the teleport map, useful for avoiding EID's TAB shortcut (MCM: OverlayKey / OverlayKeyController). Thanks @Porp!
- Scale the teleport map from 0.5x to 2.5x (MCM: MinimapScale).

FAQ

Accidentally dragged the teleport map into the trash? Restore it from MCM, or enter this command in the in-game console:
lua gt:get_config().KeyboardMapEnable=true

Original [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1630477831]GoodTrip[/url] by @tarako
Co-authored with @Porp
GitHub: https://github.com/archibate/isaacmods

┌──────────────────────────────────────────────────────────┐
│★ Check out my other fixed mod: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3169946719]TimeMachine [Fixed][/url] ★│
└──────────────────────────────────────────────────────────┘
</description>
    <version>2.2.35</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Floors"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
